Second Event
It is an early ending.
Do you have any news from Hikaru Ritsuki?
Yes, I do. Irinari and Oukun's Nationwide Never Lose Tour
On Friday, May 19 and Saturday, May 20
The tour finale will be held at Tokyo Line Cube Shibuya.
For ticket information, please see the official website Twitter.
How are you doing? For the tour final.
We are currently on tour and visiting various places,
I think we are growing up more and more.
I see. How many places are you going to tour until the end?
Uh, 12.
Twelve.
You didn't know where you were going because it was so crowded, right?
I remember.
Do you remember that?
One by one.
What? Do you remember? Every single one.
I remember.
Yes, I remember.
Of course you do.
It's a stage.
I wonder if the direction will change.
I think so.
Does that mean I should see both?
Please come to both!
The last day on the 20th is probably sold out.
Too bad. I guess I'll have to leave now.
The 19th is still available, so please come.
So there are a lot of exciting tricks to look forward to on the 19th.
We are looking forward to seeing you on the 19th.
Tomoko Inoue will be performing at Tokyo Idol Festival 2023, which will be held in Odaiba for three days from Friday, August 4 to Sunday, August 6.
Oh, wow!
Yay!
Is it that time of year already?
It's the heat.
Now, and ? And Inari Tohoku-san 2023 Grand Ichiban Live on Friday, December 29 at Pacifico Yokohama National Great Hall.
Wow.
Wow. That's amazing.
Amazing.
Is this the biggest concert ever by Tohoku-san alone?
Yes. Probably.
Yes, I think so. Have you been to the Pacifico Yokohama National Grand Hall? I have never been. Oh, really? Yes, probably! Have you been to the Grand National Hall at Pacifico Yokohama?
I've never been.
Oh, really?
First time.
It's huge!
Wow.
If we fill it with people who love Tohoku...
I'm looking forward to it!
Well, Mr. Mishima...
Can I give you a cup of tea to cheer you up, Mr. Kettle?
Oh! Yes!
Well, it's jasmine tea.
Jasmine tea! Thank you very much.
Oh, I'll have some. Mr. Kettle.
Please.
Ah! Delicious!
Really? The fresh aroma spreads through the tea.
It spreads.
It spreads? Jasmine has bloomed!
Jasmine has bloomed.
I'll choose my words.
Thank you.
I learned a lot.
It was interesting.
I'm glad you had a good time.
I had a good time.
Thank you very much.
Yes, it was fun.
I'm sorry.
No, it was fun.
To the fans in front of the camera.
May I end on a pretty note?
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you for watching.
Peco
I hope you got to know a little bit about Runchan.I hope I have learned a little bit about Run-chan.
Please continue to be a good friend.
Yes and no.
Bye bye!
Thank you.
This program,
Hartan-san
Egurun, Mattu, Kankan, and Ihinari DD Keisuke.
Thank you all very much. Let's do our best in this difficult world!